Carolyn Gabel-Brett Feminist and LGBT Collections. GLBTQ.2012.03
GLBTQ Archives
- Series III: University of Connecticut (UCONN) School of Social Work
  - National Association of Social Workers (NASW) Lesbian Gay Task Force - agendas, minutes, correspondence, mailing lists, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "Integrating Seminar on Women's Issues" SEM 340 taught by C. Gabel - course materials, [1981] (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - UCONN Professor of Social Work - notes, correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - UCONN Field Education and Supervision - evaluations, training summaries, correspondence, notes, memoranda, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - UCONN School of Social Work: Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Student Alliance - "Strategies for Change" notes, notices, reports, mailings, flyers, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - UCONN School of Social Work courses SEM 340 'Seminar on Women's Issues' and HB 373 'Violence Against Women: A Cultural Heritage' taught by C. Gabel - bibliograpies, course descriptions, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - "Violence Against Women: A Cultural Heritage" HB 371 taught by C. Gabel - course materials, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - "Why Women Stay" workshop presented by C. Gabel at social work conference, Southern Connecticut State College - conference materials, May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - "Variety of Living Styles" course, "Gay/Lesbian Families" workshop taught/presented by C. Gabel and Julio Morales - bibliography, articles, student feedback, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Domenstic Abuse Unit - communications, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Domestic Abuse Unit - questionnaire, responses, analysis, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Domestic Abuse Unit - shelter information, legislative information, notes, outlines, bibliography, correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - "Meeting the Conservative Challenge of the 80's: Women as Social Workers and Clients" National Association of Social Workers (NASW) Conference - conference materials, May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - UCONN School of Social Work field placements - descriptions, correspondence, notes, forms, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Violence Against Women" course HB 373 - bibliography, handouts, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - "Violence Against Women" course HB 373 - syllabus, student work, grades, course evaluation, correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Family Violence Conference, Fairfield County Coalition for Abused Women, C. Gabel Keynote Speaker - correspondence, article, brochure, report notes, program, fact sheet, sample press release, business card, paper, May 1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Family Violence Conference, Fairfield County Coalition for Abused Women, C. Gabel Keynote Speaker - speech, notes, correspondence, newspaper articles, May 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - "Curriculum on Battered Women: An Approach Within the Framework of Violence Against Women" presented by C. Gabel at the Council on Social Work Education Annual Program Meeting, Fort Worth, Texas, March 1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - "Sensitivity is Still Not Enough: Sixty Workshops Concerning Lesbian/Gay Issues" 2nd Annual UCONN School of Social Work Conference, National Association of Social Workers (NASW) Lesbian/Gay Task Force - conference materials, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Annual Meeting - proposal, conference, materials, address list, correspondence, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - UCONN School of Social Work: Conference on Mediation - agenda, notes, meeting minutes, May 1983 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - UCONN School of Social Work: termination of Carolyn Gabel - letters of support, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - UCONN School of Social Work Independent Study: "White Women Combatting Racism" - syllabus, articles, bibiography, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - "An Approach for Addressing Racism, Ethnocentrism, and Sexism in the Curriculum" - C. Gabel co-contributor, [1986] (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - UCONN School of Social Work: "Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual Parent and Children Conference", 1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - UCONN School of Social Work course: "New Perspectives on Lesbians and Gay Men", 1999 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - UCONN Safe Zone Project, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - UCONN School of Social Work Course Evaluations, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - UCONN School of Social Work course work - Political Systems, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - UCONN School of Social Work: Advancement of Political Social Work Practice Campaign - correspondence, agenda, map, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Series IV: Love Makes a Family (LMF)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - articles, Second Parent Adoption Act, advertisements, correspondence, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - testimony, poll, hearing, correspondence, fact sheets, clippings, 2001, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - civil unions, economic fact sheet, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - newspaper clippings, April 2005 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA) - correspondence, vote counts and comments, 2004 election summary, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - correspondence from supporting organizations: American Civil Liberties Union, People for the American Way Foundation, Latinas/Latinos for Marriage Equality, National Gay and Lesbian Task Force, Queer People of Color, Yale, UCONN, Quinnipiac University, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) Lobbying Team - meeting agendas, correspondence, notes, fact sheets, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) Political Action Committee - campaign materials, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Love Makes a Family (LMF) - press releases, notes, fundraising, grant proposal, correspondence, 2006-2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Series V: Domestic Partners
  - Domestic Partners: Health Benefits - articles, fact sheets, proposals, position paper, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - State Pride Domestic Partner Benefits - newspaper articles, legislation in other locations (France, California), correspondence, general information, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Domestic Partners: Connecticut State Pride - general information, lists, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Domestic Partner Benefits Information - local boards of education, Human Rights Campaign definition, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - "National, Connecticut State, and Selected Municipal Domestic Partner Health Benefit Policies" - memoranda, general information, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian Gay Direct Action - protest at CT state capitol, march in Bushnell Park, non-violent civil disobedience information, newspaper articles, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lesbian Gay Direct Action/Queer Nation - directory of resources, meeting minutes, statements, voting guide, clippings, protest guide, holiday card, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lesbian Gay Direct Action: interruption of Governor's Budget Address - articles, correspondence, photographs, summons, appellate brief, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "Children from the Shadows II" - conference program, March 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "Children from the Shadows" - advertisements, newspaper articles, resources for youth, 1997-2000 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - "Children from the Shadows VII: Taking LGBT Youth Issues Beyond Risk to Resilience" - conference information, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - True Colors XII Conference, Central Connecticut State University - resource guide, "Deconstructing Labels," conference program, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - True Colors XV and XVI - conference programs, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Series VI: West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case
  - West Hartford Committee for Fairness - photographs, sign-in sheets, correspondence, facilities rental contracts, notes, signs, flyers, stickers, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - West Hartford Town Council - meeting minutes, notes, voter guide, February 1998-May 2000 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - correspondence, notes, November 1998-September 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - correspondence, notes, reports, notices, October 1999-December 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - correspondence, court papers, February 2000-May 2000 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - correspondence, court papers, June 2000-December 2000 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - correspondence, court papers, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - West Hartford Cornerstone Pool Discrimination Case - newspaper clippings, press releases, 1998-2000, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Series VII: Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - New Haven Chapter Minutes, August 1986-October 1989 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - covers, flyers, clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights Bill - amendments, correspondence with religious leaders, copies of the bill, Massachusetts Gay and Lesbian Political Caucus Lobby Day information, 1987, 1990, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Steering Committee minutes, December 1987- April 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - correspondence with politicians and institutions in CT, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Steering Committee policies/proposals, 1988, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights Bill - State Senate summary report, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - By-laws, January 17, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Steering Committee minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - budget, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Mercy Center Retreat - description of activity, goals, action plans, [1990] (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Legislative Report by Elizabeth Gallo and Barry Williams (Gallo and Williams Government Relations, West Hartford), correspondence with Elizabeth Gallo, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - "An Act Concerning Discrimination on the Basis of Sexual Orientation" law passed April 17, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Political Action Committee (PAC) - meeting minutes, proposal for steering committee, press releases, budgets, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - materials about organizing for legislative issues, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Lesbian and Gay Rights Coalition Political Action Committee - Connecticut State Elections Enforcement Commission letters, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - mailing lists, 1998, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Steering Committee correspondence, agendas, event advertising, workshops/conferences, member list, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Legislative Breakfast - program, floppy disk with program on it, sign-in sheet, name tags, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)/National Gay and Lesbian Task Force - Equality Begins at Home articles, pin, mailers, events, Rainbow Flag Rally, Metroline, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - official history by Denise Frances, 1992; research notes, 2001-2003; "The Legal Rights of Lesbians, Gay Men and Bisexuals in Connecticut," 1997; correspondence and minutes 1993-2001, 1992-2003 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)/Stonewall - correspondence, event advertisements, meetings with legislators, meeting agendas/minutes, receipts, press releases, handwritten notes, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - newsletter, handouts, mailings, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Haymarket People's Fund Diversity Project - interviews, grant application, original proposal, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) National Gay and Lesbian Task Force - Equality Begins At Home Press Kit (2), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Legislative Breakfast - sign-in sheet, notes, program, floppy disk with program on it; October 7, 2000, October 2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Steering Committee correspondence, agendas, event advertising, workshops/conferences, member list, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) Diversity Project - meeting agendas, minutes, notes, receipts, correspondence, description of project, interview questions for coordinator, applicant's paperwork, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - Diversity Project Focus Group Report, celebration dinner/meeting program and planning, correspondence, notes, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - minutes, reports, fact sheets, conference information, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - meeting agenda/minutes, notes, CRS Report for Congress "Public Aid and Faith-Based Organizations (Charitable Choice)," opposition to nomination of John Ashcroft for Attorney General, list of federal and state officials, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) - meeting agenda, newspaper article, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)/Stonewall - mail and email addresses, official mailing lists, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR)/Stonewall - mail and email addresses, various handwritten notes, undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Series VIII: Marriage Equality and LGBT miscellaneous issues
  - GLBTQ miscellaneous events, n.d.; Center for Disease Control weekly report regarding the prevention of HIV, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - GLBT people-empolyment discrimination - flyers, fact sheets, 1990's (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Civil Rights (CCLGCR) photo of State of the State Address by Governor O'Neill interrupted by Coalition, February 1990 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gay Rights Bill signing ceremony - photos and clippings, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Candellight Vigil - notes, meeting minutes, correspondence, press release, articles, flyers, October 1992 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - AIDS Action Network - correspondence, notes, flyers, petition, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Lesbian/Gay Task Force on Federal Legislation - correspondence, notes, flyers, action kit, meeting minutes, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - National Minority AIDS Council - conference materials, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies Training - information, articles on homosexuality, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Articles from Metroline, GLA Bulletin, Newsweek, and Hartford Courant, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii Same Sex Marriage - correspondence, articles, fact sheets, Marriage Project-Hawaii documents, Office of Health Status Monitoring forms for marriage license, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Defense of Marriage Act (DOMA) - opposition information, newspaper articles, amendment strategies, correspondence, issues in other states, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Freedom to Marry/National Freedom to Marry Day - correspondence, Vermont legislation articles, The Marriage Project, Lambda Legal Defense Fund, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund (CWEALF) Latina Event - newspaper articles, agenda notes, planning meeting minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force: Establishment of the Federation of Statewide LGBT Political Organizations - correspondence, mailing list, proposal outlines, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (CHRO) Transgender Issues - press releases; "Declaratory Ruling on Behalf of John/Jane Doe;" petition; newspaper articles; publications from Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders, The Human Rights Campaign, It's Time Connecticut, and the Gay Lesbian, and Straight Education Network; The Advocate article "Transgendered", 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Co-Parent Adoption in Connecticut - articles, correspondence, mailing list, "Baby Z Case," legislator lists, Civil Liberty News, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Pride Link: a Resource Guide of Lesbian/Gay/Bisexual/Transgender Organizations-Connecticut Women's Education and Legal Fund, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rainbow Flag at Connecticut State Capitol - photographs of speakers, protestor, "outing" Patrick Flaherty, film negatives, March 21, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Out! Awards - program, Hartford October 2, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Veronica Berrill Case: Berrill v. Houde - correspondence, newspaper articles, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - LGBT articles: Gays in the Military, 1999; Newsweek, March 2000, 1999, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - LGBT Herstory/History Project Questionnaire; "Herstory and History of St. Francis, St. Clare Parish of the American Apostolic Catholic Church," West Hartford, CT, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Alfred Stieglitz, Georgia O'Keeffe, and American Modernism Exhibit at the Wadsworth Atheneum news release; Biography of artist Marsden Hartley; Design, Dance, and Music of the Ballet Russes exhibit; Shorter article version (Richard Nelson), June 9, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Institute for Community Research: Sexual Minority Youth Project - memo, program, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - National Conference for Community and Justice: Sexual Orientation - correspondence, reports, lists, brochure, notes, education materials, 1999, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - "Just the Facts About Sexual Orientation and Youth: A Primer for Principals, Educators, and School Personnel" publication, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Institute for Community Research LGBT Project - correspondence, fact sheets, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Vermont LGBT Marriage Civil Rights - correspondence, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Connecticut Commission on Human Rights and Opportunities (CHRO) - testimony of Leslie Brett re: State Empolyee's Campaign Request for Declaratory Ruling Concerning Inclusion of Boy Scouts in Charitable Giving Campaign; related materials, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - "OUT and Into the Voting Booth: Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Voters in 2000," a report by the Gill Foundation (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Hartford Gay and Lesbian Health Collective Gill Foundation Workshops - correspondence, flyers, fact sheets, brochure, forms, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Connecticut Civil Liberties Union - "Reasons for Connecticut to Oppose a Same-Sex Marriage Ban," domestic partnership facts, "Privacy Rights in Connecticut" booklet, annual message, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - "GLAD (Gay and Lesbian Advocates and Defenders) Files Suit to End Connecticut's Exclusion of Lesbian and Gay Couples from Marriage Rights" - legal papers, press releases, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - "Counting on Couples: Fiscal Savings from Allowing Same-Sex Couples to Marry in Connecticut," The Williams Project, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Same-sex couples' right to marry - clippings, 2006-2008 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - "Who's Behind the Gay Rights Movement?" publication of the National Gay Task Force, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Series IX: Connecticut Stonewall Congress
  - "Time Line Project" Resources/Records - Stonewall Riots, legislation, sources taken from different archives, letters to sponsors, drafts of timeline, revisions, 1987-1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress/Stonewall Coalition - articles, legislative proposals, notes, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation - reports, to the CT Secretary of State, 1994-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Stonewall Congress - mailing lists, part 1, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Stonewall Congress - mailing lists, part 2, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation - membership lists, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stonewall Foundation - notes, membership list, letters, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress - events and flyers, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress - newsletter, brochure, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress - "Celebrating Our Stories, Embracing Our Future" Trinity College - program; photos of speakers, booths, exhibits, attendees (two envelopes); October 4, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress - Stonewall Annual Report, 1997 and Reorganization by-laws, 1998, 1999, 1997, 1998, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Congress - meeting agendas, written notes, annual report (disk), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Conference/Exhibit - program, correspondence, notes, registration slips, planning materials, speaker biographies: October 23 and 27, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation "Challenging and Changing America: The Struggle for Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Civil Rights" - conference materials, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation "Challenging and Changing America: An Exhibition on the Struggle for Gay, Bisexual, Transgender Civil Rights" Hartford Public Library - guest book, October 1999 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Timeline Exhibit Project, Thomas J. Dodd Research Center at the University of Connecticut - program, resources contact list, newspaper articles, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation documentary video "ONE Step Towards Justice, The Passage of the Connecticut Gay Rights Bill" - agendas, minutes, notes, correspondence, mailing lists, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation Challenging and Changing America Timeline Exhibit - fundraising letters, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation - email and address lists, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation/Community Works - contributors, vendor card report, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation "Challenging and Changing America" Exhibit at the Elihu Burritt Library, Central Connecticut State University - program, material from advertising, June-July 2000 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation Board-Potential Candidates - correspondence, notes, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Connecticut Stonewall Foundation/CWEALF Panel on Hate Crimes - mailing list, receipts, documents on floppy disk, flyers, correspondence, notes, diversity news articles, October 25, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 23)